<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on krymancer.dev</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on krymancer.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.153.1</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:39:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>09 10x Improvment Game</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/09-10x-improvment-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:39:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/09-10x-improvment-game/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To be fair, I did not work on the game for a while, and since the last time I wrote about in here I had made A LOT of changes, I implemented ECS instead of using a more OO approach and basically rewrote the entire thing. I was trying to make the gameplay more exciting so I was pretty invested on writing code for the bee behavior (I shoud give you some background here but the game was kinda an POC and nothing really worked, you can &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/03-devlog-buzz/&#34;&gt;read the other post about it &lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>06 Search Is Dead</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/06-search-is-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:05:34 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/06-search-is-dead/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At this point I expect you to realize that search is dead, no it wasn&amp;rsquo;t because of LLM&amp;rsquo;s, those just made it clearer sooner, and as much as I have the incorporation of AI on every single thing on earth it was not AI faults, at least not in the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started using computers from a very young age, at least in my community, like 7 or 8 years old. My internet was BAD, I mean it, BAD, in the later 2000&amp;rsquo;s internet was not too bad, at least not in where I live, but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford it, so I used some 2 digit Kbps internet for a lot of time. This with being an impatient child made me optimize a lot of things that I did in the computer, for download games, videos, and most importantly searching.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>04 Back to Arch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/04-back-to-arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:01:20 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/04-back-to-arch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t remember exactly when I started to using linux, probably I had my frist real contact in 2014 trying ubuntu, debian and kali. It was years latter, in college, that I tried to run daily. I was so comfortable in windows so I didn&amp;rsquo;t really saw an reason to change. Debian was my first daily option, I was in a class about embedded systems programming and we need to use a gcc cross compiler, some programs to create linux images, copy code to development boards memory and stuff. The professor really wanted us to use linux, my colleges dual booted their machines but I took this as an opportunity to really try to daily drive linux.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>03 Devlog Buzz</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/03-devlog-buzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 01:27:14 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/03-devlog-buzz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in my journey of trying to learn zig on one of those days when I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get myself to sleep I thought, why not make a game using zig? Yes, the question is always &amp;ldquo;why?&amp;rdquo; and the answer is always &amp;ldquo;why not?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So another one of my phases began, I started looking into some lib or anything that I cloud make an 2d game, I was thinking in using &lt;a href=&#34;https://libsdl.org/&#34;&gt;SDL&lt;/a&gt; as I already use it in the past with C++, but I remembered &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.raylib.com/index.html&#34;&gt;raylib&lt;/a&gt; and found out about &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Not-Nik/raylib-zig&#34;&gt;raylib-zig&lt;/a&gt; and was an sign for me to start.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a JSON Parser in Rust</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/02-cc-json-parser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:22:57 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/02-cc-json-parser/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently took on a challenge to build my own JSON parser in Rust. This project was a fantastic opportunity to dive deep into parsing techniques, which are crucial for everything from simple data formats to building compilers. You can find the full details of the challenge &lt;a href=&#34;https://codingchallenges.fyi/challenges/challenge-json-parser&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and the source code in my &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Krymancer/cc-json-parser&#34;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-challenge&#34;&gt;The Challenge&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The challenge was structured to incrementally build a JSON parser, starting with simple JSON objects and progressively handling more complex structures. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step breakdown of the process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building my own wc Tool in Rust</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-cc-wt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 18:08:37 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-cc-wt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I found myself not really excited to code anything and that was really bothering me. I was always excited to code something, learning something new and not being able to enjoy it or have the motivation to do it was really driving me crazy. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what was the cause but I can&amp;rsquo;t do anytthing, I felt like I was justing being lazy, tried to read a book, or take a time for myself but nothing really helped. So I started to serching for a new project that I cloud make and be excited about, nothing really caught my eye, same basic projects as aways, frontend projects are either too simple or have some gimmic that I didn&amp;rsquo;t really care at the moment, backend projects are always CRUD at this point. I was really lost, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do, I was really sad about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Zig API</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/00-demo-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:50:06 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/00-demo-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s this event, which is conceived by Zanfranceschi. Essentially, Zan gave us a specification that we followed to implement an API. For this first quarter edition of 2024, we have a kind of &amp;ldquo;Bank&amp;rdquo; where some pre-registered clients check their statements and make transactions. If you want to read more details, I invite you to take a look at the repository of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/zanfranceschi/rinha-de-backend-2024-q1&#34;&gt;event&lt;/a&gt;, where you can find the specifications along with the rest of the participation instructions and related information.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
