<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>krymancer.dev</title>
    <link>https://krymancer.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on krymancer.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.137.0</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:45:49 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://krymancer.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I really hate AI</title>
      <link>https://krymancer.dev/posts/03-burnout/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:45:49 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://krymancer.dev/posts/03-burnout/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ins&amp;rsquo;t news that OpenAI released ChatGPT into the wild of the internet and it become the most rapidly used product ever (don&amp;rsquo;t check me on that I cloud be wrong). People started using it for everything and I mean everything. I saw it in websites, I saw it in software and products that really don&amp;rsquo;t beneficiate even a little bit in having all might &amp;ldquo;AI&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ts almost impossible now days getting support for a product because of the chat bots that don&amp;rsquo;t help at all, a FAQ would be better, cost less and don&amp;rsquo;t harm the environment as much. I decided to write this after I read &lt;a href=&#34;https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2024/01/02/the-i-in-llm-stands-for-intelligence/&#34;&gt;this incredible post&lt;/a&gt; by Daniel Stenberg. You might already know what it is and where this is going.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building My Own JSON Parser in Rust</title>
      <link>https://krymancer.dev/posts/02-cc-json-parser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:22:57 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://krymancer.dev/posts/02-cc-json-parser/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently took on a challenge to build my own JSON parser in Rust. This project was a fantastic opportunity to dive deep into parsing techniques, which are crucial for everything from simple data formats to building compilers. You can find the full details of the challenge &lt;a href=&#34;https://codingchallenges.fyi/challenges/challenge-json-parser&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and the source code in my &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Krymancer/cc-json-parser&#34;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-challenge&#34;&gt;The Challenge&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The challenge was structured to incrementally build a JSON parser, starting with simple JSON objects and progressively handling more complex structures. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step breakdown of the process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Coding Chalenge] - Building my Own wc Tool in Rust</title>
      <link>https://krymancer.dev/posts/01-cc-wt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 18:08:37 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://krymancer.dev/posts/01-cc-wt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I found myself not really excited to code anything and that was really bothering me. I was always excited to code something, learning something new and not being able to enjoy it or have the motivation to do it was really driving me crazy. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what was the cause but I can&amp;rsquo;t do anytthing, I felt like I was justing being lazy, tried to read a book, or take a time for myself but nothing really helped. So I started to serching for a new project that I cloud make and be excited about, nothing really caught my eye, same basic projects as aways, frontend projects are either too simple or have some gimmic that I didn&amp;rsquo;t really care at the moment, backend projects are always CRUD at this point. I was really lost, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do, I was really sad about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Zig API</title>
      <link>https://krymancer.dev/posts/00-demo-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:50:06 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://krymancer.dev/posts/00-demo-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s this event, which is conceived by Zanfranceschi. Essentially, Zan gave us a specification that we followed to implement an API. For this first quarter edition of 2024, we have a kind of &amp;ldquo;Bank&amp;rdquo; where some pre-registered clients check their statements and make transactions. If you want to read more details, I invite you to take a look at the repository of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/zanfranceschi/rinha-de-backend-2024-q1&#34;&gt;event&lt;/a&gt;, where you can find the specifications along with the rest of the participation instructions and related information.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
